https://natfire.com/privacy-policy/

HomePrivacy Policy
This privacy policy is intended for all users of National Fireproofing Supply Co.
National Fireproofing Supply Company is dedicated to respecting and protecting the privacy of our clients. All information you provide, such as E-mail addresses or any additional personal information on or through any forms found on our site, will be used solely to support your relationship with National Fireproofing Supply Company. We strive to develop innovative methods to better serve our users. Our services are designed and operate with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use National Fireproofing Supply Company services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. By visiting this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.
This privacy policy addresses the following areas:
What personally identifiable information National Fireproofing Supply Company collects.What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the web site.What organization collects the information.How National Fireproofing Supply Company uses the information.With whom National Fireproofing, Inc may share user information.What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the control of National Fireproofing, IncHow users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact National Fireproofing Supply Company. Any violation of this privacy policy will lead to suspension of user privileges and permanent removal from access to this web site.
Information Collection:
Unless described otherwise in this privacy policy, National Fireproofing Supply Company will not sell any information. All information collected by National Fireproofing Supply Company will be used solely by National Fireproofing Supply Company to deliver targeted newsletters and advertisements.
Information Use – Profiles:
National Fireproofing Supply Company stores information collected through cookies, log files and/or third interests in your user profile. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users detailing specific viewing preferences. Subsequently, this collected information is linked to users’ personally identifiable information,which provides directs pertinent marketing promotions to you and helps us improve site content for the user. National Fireproofing Supply Company does not share your profile with other third parties, unless specifically mentioned elsewhere in this policy.Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Cookies, if used, will be used on National Fireproofing Supply Company to remember and recall login names, login information, previous purchases, potential purchases, as well as other items to help us better understand users’ needs. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use National Fireproofing Supply Company. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. For more details, see the above “Profile” section. We have no control over any third party that may also use cookies to store personal information. However, we do not provide this information to any third party.
Log Files:
Like most standard web site servers we may use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, site administer, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.Sharing – Legal Disclaimer
Though we exercise all due caution to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. This includes, but is not limited to, any defense to any claim in which National Fireproofing Supply Company is a defendant, to assist in any investigations by law enforcement agencies, or violations of any National Fireproofing Supply Company policy.
Links:
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, National Fireproofing Supply Company, are not responsible for the privacy practices of sites other than our own. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. National Fireproofing Supply Company may have co-branding and/or framing relations with other companies. In this case, you should be familiar with the privacy policies of both companies, since you may be subject to each of them.
Contacting National Fireproofing Supply Company: If you have questions or concerns about the National Fireproofing Supply Company guidelines, policies, and procedures.
Security: Notification of Changes:
If we decide to change our privacy policy, changes will be posted to this privacy statement, our homepage, and other places we deem conspicuous and appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. National Fireproofing Supply Company will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, users will be notified via e-mail. Users will then be presented with a choice as to whether or not we become authorized to use their information in this different way. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users (who have opted to receive communications from National Fireproofing Supply Company), notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
National Fireproofing Supply Co, Inc. and its affiliates maintain professional standards and have a high quality of respect to our members as well as our guest and affiliates
About Us
Products
Fire Retardant Spray Products
UL Fire Stopping Products
Contact Us
My Account
Blog
Legal
© 2020 National Fireproofing, Inc. All rights reserved.
Scroll to Top
